I'll see you in the next video, bye!
Neon eyes and conspiracy dreams
Talking cults in the desert sands
Tattoo maps and shaking hands
She's got screenshots, names and date
A ten-four halo, ceiling face in a chatroom chapel
Saints confess every broadcast feels like a holy mass
She's cookie, she's hot, she might be right
Dropping bombs in the middle of the night
White rose, black vans, symbols sex
Oh Lord, what will she say next?
Crazy clothes, games and traffickers
Little Saboteurs, truth or fiction doesn't matter much
She's fire and static and socketed
She's part oracle, part in a net myth, half the room's scared
The rest subsist, her eyeline are as sharp as a truth
I said it, and every theory leaves the chat infected
You can laugh, but you're still tuned in
Because she's chaos wrapped in porcelain skin
Lies in shadow
got the big screen. Take me off the big screen. Hello. Alright. Why did you laugh at me that
I got phone bombs? Who got you? Nobody got me because I I always win. So I hate this
shit. Oh, it's okay. I don't have to handle it. I'm just childish like you. I know it
was it was Tony or just Tony Baloney. Okay, but it's fine.
It's coming in 10 minutes, and then it came right away, so I just need to make sure it's a real ghost
Ghost yeah, put that shit on foreign in here. Yeah
Yeah, so let's see
Okay, okay, you guys talk for a second cuz I'm uh, I'm doing something for my website
Okay. I'll be right. I'll be right. I'll be right. Okay. Let me talk to this dumb dumb then
Hello dumb dumb hang on
He obviously just said let's talk and you just need to yourself
Hey, dum-dum
Fuckin' majority
If you're going to meet yourself as soon as you laugh, it makes a lot of sounds, right?
But we're going to return.
You'd like to not meet yourself.
Okay, there we go.
How are you doing, sir?
That was kind of fucking your chart.
You're going to meet yourself.
What are you still talking? I'm sorry. Go ahead.
Nothing. There's like pulling teeth at this point. Will you say something?
I don't know for fuck's sake.
Hey dum-dum, can you hear me?
Hey dum-dum
Jesus Christ pulling teeth around here fucking too stupid even talk
You're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna talk, you're gonna
You can be nice and I would have a conversation, but yeah, I could be nice. I could be nice. Oh, is it my tone?
You know what two plus two, you know what two is. Thank you
You know what two plus two is fucking four. Is it my tone?
Listen, that was awkward as fuck. You just waited five fucking minutes. So what what what kind of point are you trying to prove here?
Who said I'm trying to prove a point? Oh, yeah, you're trying to prove a point
My set there being all quiet shit you fucking weirdo
So you don't the fuck you're talking about do you
Okay, it's like he doesn't want to talk then I'm just gonna end the panel because
Like dance for me monkey
Just like how a conversation and like I have silence on my panel. It's like death
Like I'm not the only one here goes to talking to you. He said hey
I'm dumb and saying dance for me monkey. I'm not gonna dance for him
I want you to dance for me. Can you put on a speedo and get in my lap? Well, then let's go private
Okay, really?
Adios, baby. Yeah
No, oh you suck
Are you sure
You wanna see my dick
Hebrew hammer
Do you leave
Okay, goes I'm gonna send it he's not cooperating he doesn't want to
Do you leave?
Hello, I'm just gonna end the stream. Okay. No one wants to fuck with me. Okay. Have a good night
Thanks a lot.